<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>kulat.co</title>
    <link>http://kulat.co/</link>
    <description>Recent content on kulat.co</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://kulat.co/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>http://kulat.co/post/placeholder/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kulat.co/post/placeholder/</guid>
      <description>##Here&amp;rsquo;s my first post!
Felt like refactoring my website to make it easier to write blog posts and record my experiences at this point in my career. Now, the blog posts can have simple tags and are all written in full markdown, so the styling is customizable and real easy.
Currently, I plan on updating this site with tidbits on what I&amp;rsquo;ve learned, and the projects I&amp;rsquo;ve completed as a part of my portfolio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://kulat.co/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kulat.co/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Christian, a software engineer currently living in the Atlanta area. I&amp;rsquo;ve been studying programming for 6 years now, and I&amp;rsquo;m looking for an opportunity to contribute to your team!
My main programming tools are Go and Python - I have enjoy building small scripts, single page applications, testing suites and bots for the online chat and community service Discord. I try and approach these problems by writing the most efficient and beautiful code possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Me</title>
      <link>http://kulat.co/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kulat.co/contact/</guid>
      <description>Always feel free to reach out! I&amp;rsquo;d love to discuss any new opportunities or answer any questions about my background.
In the meantime, I&amp;rsquo;m going to continue working on projects and occasionally writes blog posts about career updates, project&amp;rsquo;s I&amp;rsquo;m working on, or bits of information I&amp;rsquo;ve learned that I found interesting!
The easiest way to reach me is with email: cdkulat1@gmail.com
Feel free to also reach out with LinkedIn or Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christian Kulat&#39;s Resume</title>
      <link>http://kulat.co/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://kulat.co/resume/</guid>
      <description>Christian Kulat I’m a full-stack software engineer creating functional and beautiful code primarily in Python and Go. Based in Atlanta, I’ve been studying software development since 2017 and am looking to join a team to help both the company and myself grow. I’m comfortable with version control and technical writing, and am interested in building microservices for the cloud! I’m still learning every day, and am looking forward to taking ahold of every opportunity handed to me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
